{
    "id": "51ba5575deab40c3a3ecb926fd682c4f",
    "title": "General English Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Space research has been growing by leaps and ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bounds",
                "fits",
                "starts"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5182fa414b124d4e80c4083b356764bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "The duty of space scientists is to …………………. the mysteries of the universe.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unravel",
                "identify",
                "disclose",
                "diagnose"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d657258273fe4fbbadd1bfd5b1966bff"
        },
        {
            "question": "The government assured the Supreme Court that it has taken all steps to ………………….. the formation of the new state.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "expedite",
                "extract",
                "accelerate"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2db2a82a215a4776a5fb82a3296e2683"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ..................... of his statement are far-reaching.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "applications",
                "implications",
                "allusions",
                "consequences"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "354208a8332a442fb13a7c294882e9d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have eaten your ..................... . number of pizza slices.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "allowed",
                "allotted",
                "subscribed",
                "prescribed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "998c5c02f26043a09c369d1d3c4ae0f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonym of Calumny",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "encomium",
                "veritable",
                "slander",
                "virtuous"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b28adfc60dfc4312bb123b6bb57eb661"
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonyms of  Anathema",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "blessing",
                "curse",
                "potent",
                "privileged"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f8830b4a5ef5428fbf0c45e53e13ae60"
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonym of Disparate",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Similar",
                "Dissimilar",
                "Ordinary",
                "Authentic"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8bf8483690fe442098c8a8732805ee49"
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonym of Interdict",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Allow",
                "Approve",
                "Appreciate",
                "Prohibit"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "7591061eeeab4e559c1f4c5114543c85"
        },
        {
            "question": "Synonym of Inveterate",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Chronic",
                "Irate",
                "Curable",
                "Corrigible"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49ab1e8694d84743ae82a828ff2cece2"
        }
    ]
}